<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="assets/xml/rss.xsl" media="all"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Anthony Tanbakuchi</title><link>http://tanbakuchi.com/</link><description>Personal site of Anthony Tanbakuchi, PhD.</description><atom:link rel="self" href="http://tanbakuchi.com/rss.xml" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2016 02:02:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>https://getnikola.com/</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Welcome to my updated site</title><link>http://tanbakuchi.com/posts/welcome-to-my-updated-site/</link><dc:creator>Anthony Tanbakuchi</dc:creator><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since my long time hosting provider BlueHost kept increasing prices and I don't
need any advanced features that they offer, I decided to move my site to Github Pages
since I'm already a Github user.
My site has been statically generated for years. The advantages of a static site are
(1) it makes hosting simple,  (2) it is very secure compared to dynamic sites,
and (3) I am not locked into any platform. I updated my static
generator code to Python based &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://getnikola.com"&gt;Nikola&lt;/a&gt; from
Ruby based &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://webgen.gettalong.org"&gt;WebGen&lt;/a&gt;. I made this change
because I prefer Python and I like the option to be able to include iPython posts.
By making these changes I was able to save about $160/year due to BlueHost's newly
announced major price increases. My only cost now
is my domain registration
since Github Pages are free. Much thanks to the great community services at Github!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All of the content that was available on the previous site is still here. Just
use the menu at the top to access everything.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><guid>http://tanbakuchi.com/posts/welcome-to-my-updated-site/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2016 19:46:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A polarization system for persistent chemical detection</title><link>http://tanbakuchi.com/posts/a-polarization-system-for-persistent-chemical-detection/</link><dc:creator>Anthony Tanbakuchi</dc:creator><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="figure"&gt;
&lt;img alt="/Papers/2015PolarizationSystem.jpg" src="http://tanbakuchi.com/Papers/2015PolarizationSystem.jpg"&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was a conference paper that I was a co-author on where we developed a infrared
polarization system for chemical detection.
My contribution was the
design, tolerancing, building, and testing of the optical system. The goal was to
make a low cost short wave thermal imager (SWIR) to test polarization detection
for certain chemicals. You can read the details in the
&lt;a class="reference external" href="http://tanbakuchi.com/Papers/2015PolarizationSystem.pdf"&gt;paper&lt;/a&gt;. The design was very successful for
the intended application as a first generation prototype. It was optimized
for loose tolerances, easy fabrication of the optical elements, and passive
assembly. By making the optics fit into a commercial telescope focuser and
building some simple custom adaptors we turned something that could have cost many
tens of thousands of dollars into an instrument that was only a few thousand dollars.
Moreover, we were able to utilize rapid prototype parts for the filter holder enabling
us to have more complex parts in that component without driving fabrication costs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Citation: Julia Craven-Jones, Leah Appelhans, Eric Couphos, Todd Embree, Patrick Finnegan,
Dennis Goldstein, David Karelitz, Charles LaCasse, Ting S. Luk,
Adoum Mahamat, Lee Massey, Anthony Tanbakuchi, Cody Washburn, Steven Vigil,
&lt;em&gt;"A polarization system for persistent chemical detection,"&lt;/em&gt;
Proc. SPIE. 9613, Polarization Science and Remote Sensing VII, 96130B.
September 01, 2015 doi: 10.1117/12.2188718
&lt;a class="reference external" href="http://tanbakuchi.com/Papers/2015PolarizationSystem.pdf"&gt;PDF&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><category>publications</category><guid>http://tanbakuchi.com/posts/a-polarization-system-for-persistent-chemical-detection/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2015 00:54:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Practical implementation of broadband diffractive optical elements</title><link>http://tanbakuchi.com/posts/practical-implementation-of-broadband-diffractive-optical-elements/</link><dc:creator>Anthony Tanbakuchi</dc:creator><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="figure"&gt;
&lt;img alt="/Papers/2013DiffractiveOptics.jpg" src="http://tanbakuchi.com/Papers/2013DiffractiveOptics.jpg"&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this paper we discuss the practical modeling, design, and testing of a hybrid
diffractive optical system. My contribution to this project was proposing the idea
and helping with the implementation. You can read more in the
&lt;a class="reference external" href="http://tanbakuchi.com/Papers/2013DiffractiveOptics.pdf"&gt;paper&lt;/a&gt;. You can also read the public
Sandia National Laboratories &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://tanbakuchi.com/Papers/2013DiffractiveSand.pdf"&gt;SAND report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Citation: Junoh Choi; Alvaro A. Cruz-Cabrera; Anthony Tanbakuchi,
&lt;em&gt;"Practical implementation of broadband diffractive optical elements"&lt;/em&gt;,
Proc. SPIE. 8612, Micromachining and Microfabrication Process Technology XVIII, 86120G.
March 09, 2013 doi: 10.1117/12.2013204
&lt;a class="reference external" href="http://tanbakuchi.com/Papers/2013DiffractiveOptics.pdf"&gt;PDF&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><category>publications</category><guid>http://tanbakuchi.com/posts/practical-implementation-of-broadband-diffractive-optical-elements/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2013 01:07:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Optical design and performance testing of an athermal SWIR gas correlation imager</title><link>http://tanbakuchi.com/posts/optical-design-and-performance-testing-of-an-athermal-swir-gas-correlation-imager/</link><dc:creator>Anthony Tanbakuchi</dc:creator><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="figure"&gt;
&lt;img alt="/Papers/2012Athermal.jpg" src="http://tanbakuchi.com/Papers/2012Athermal.jpg"&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this paper I present a dual channel 7 degree full field of view f/2.5 athermal
optical design athermalized from 0 to 50 degrees C that operates in the wavelength range of 2.0 to 2.5
microns suitable for methane imaging. The system was designed to image in the field.
I was responsible for the optical design,
tolerance budget, alignment plan, and peformance testing of the system.
Predicted and as-built performance data including interferometric and
ensquared energy measurements for both imaging channels are also shown in the
&lt;a class="reference external" href="http://tanbakuchi.com/Papers/2012Athermal.pdf"&gt;paper&lt;/a&gt;. The as-built optical system meet the design
requirements and preformed well in the field.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Citation: A. Tanbakuchi; M. Smith; J. Mercier; S. Vigil; T. Embree; A. Ison,
&lt;em&gt;"Optical design and performance testing of an athermal SWIR gas correlation imager,"&lt;/em&gt;
Proc. SPIE. 8491, Optical System Alignment, Tolerancing, and Verification VI,
84910B. October 15, 2012 doi: 10.1117/12.928001
&lt;a class="reference external" href="http://tanbakuchi.com/Papers/2012Athermal.pdf"&gt;PDF&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><category>publications</category><guid>http://tanbakuchi.com/posts/optical-design-and-performance-testing-of-an-athermal-swir-gas-correlation-imager/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2012 01:14:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A multi-point scanner for high frame rate confocal microendoscopy</title><link>http://tanbakuchi.com/posts/a-multi-point-scanner-for-high-frame-rate-confocal-microendoscopy/</link><dc:creator>Anthony Tanbakuchi</dc:creator><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="figure"&gt;
&lt;img alt="/Papers/2010Confocal.jpg" src="http://tanbakuchi.com/Papers/2010Confocal.jpg"&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slit-scanning geometries for confocal microendoscopy represent a compromise
between acquisition rate and optical performance.
Such systems provide high frame rates that freeze motion but recent
Monte Carlo simulations show that scattered light severely limits the
practical imaging depth for in vivo applications. A new multi-point scanning
architecture for confocal microendoscopy has been developed. The new scanner
is based on a relatively simple modification to the slit-scanning geometry that
results in a parallelized point-scanning confocal microendoscope that maintains
the high frame rate of a slit-scanning system while providing optical performance
close to that of a single point scanning system. You can read the details in
the &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://tanbakuchi.com/Papers/2010Confocal.pdf"&gt;paper&lt;/a&gt;. This paper arose from my
&lt;a class="reference external" href="http://tanbakuchi.com/Papers/2009_TanbakuchiDissertation.pdf"&gt;dissertation&lt;/a&gt;
and &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://tanbakuchi.com/posts/a-multi-point-scanner-for-high-frame-rate-confocal-microendoscopy/2009_JBO_Monte_Carlo_Tanbakuchi"&gt;journal publication&lt;/a&gt; where I was able
to demonstrate through monte-carlo modeling that
a slit scan system could be improved by making a small modification so that it
becomes a multi-point scan system. My contribution was mainly the suggestion
of the multi-point concept, Andy and Houssine did all the hard work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Citation: Andrew R. Rouse; Houssine Makhlouf; Anthony A. Tanbakuchi; Arthur F. Gmitro,
&lt;em&gt;"A multi-point scanner for high frame rate confocal microendoscopy"&lt;/em&gt;
Proc. SPIE. 7558, Endoscopic Microscopy V, 755809. February 11, 2010 doi: 10.1117/12.842782
&lt;a class="reference external" href="http://tanbakuchi.com/Papers/2010Confocal.pdf"&gt;PDF&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><category>publications</category><guid>http://tanbakuchi.com/posts/a-multi-point-scanner-for-high-frame-rate-confocal-microendoscopy/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2010 01:22:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Real-Time Confocal Microendoscope Poster</title><link>http://tanbakuchi.com/posts/real-time-confocal-microendoscope-poster/</link><dc:creator>Anthony Tanbakuchi</dc:creator><description>&lt;div class="figure"&gt;
&lt;a class="reference external image-reference" href="http://tanbakuchi.com/Papers/2008ClinicalImagingSystem-75dpi.pdf"&gt;&lt;img alt="/Papers/2008ClinicalImagingSystem-750px.jpg" class="islink" src="http://tanbakuchi.com/Papers/2008ClinicalImagingSystem-750px.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;p class="caption"&gt;While at the University of Arizona, my colleagues and I were developing
this instrument in the &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://bil.arizona.edu"&gt;Biomedical Imaging Laboratory, Department of
Radiology&lt;/a&gt;. The long term goal of this
instrument is to replace biopsies with live video images of the cells so
surgeons can precisely isolate cancerous tumors for resection. You can
read more about it in my
&lt;a class="reference external" href="http://tanbakuchi.com/Papers/2009_TanbakuchiDissertation.pdf"&gt;dissertation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description><category>publications</category><guid>http://tanbakuchi.com/posts/real-time-confocal-microendoscope-poster/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2008 03:01:24 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>