<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../assets/xml/rss.xsl" media="all"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Anthony Tanbakuchi (publication)</title><link>http://tanbakuchi.com/</link><description></description><atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://tanbakuchi.com/categories/publication.xml"></atom:link><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2016 13:11:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>https://getnikola.com/</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>In vivo imaging of ovarian tissue using a novel confocal microlaparoscope</title><link>http://tanbakuchi.com/posts/in-vivo-imaging-of-ovarian-tissue-using-a-novel-confocal-microlaparoscope/</link><dc:creator>Anthony Tanbakuchi</dc:creator><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="figure"&gt;
&lt;img alt="/Papers/2010AJOG_Clinical_Tanbakuchi.jpg" src="http://tanbakuchi.com/Papers/2010AJOG_Clinical_Tanbakuchi.jpg"&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The objective of the study was to develop a clinical confo- cal microlaparoscope
for imaging ovary epithelium in vivo with the long- term objective of diagnosing
cancer in vivo. A confocal microlaparoscope was developed and used to image the
ovaries of 21 patients in vivo using fluorescein sodium and acridine orange as
the fluorescent contrast agents. The device was tested in vivo and demonstrated
to be safe and function as designed. Real-time cellular visualization of ovary
epithelium was demonstrated. The confocal microlaparoscope represents a new type
of in vivo imaging device. With its ability to image cellular details in real
time, it has the potential to aid in the early diagnosis of cancer. Initially
the device may be used to locate unusual regions for guided biopsies. In the
long term, the device may be able to supplant traditional biopsies and allow
the surgeon to identify early-stage ovarian cancer.
You can read the full &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://tanbakuchi.com/Papers/2010AJOG_Clinical_Tanbakuchi.pdf"&gt;journal article&lt;/a&gt;.
Below is a video from the instrument in use.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe width="459" height="344" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/HbQFZHAFMhY?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;p&gt;This publication represented 1 of 3 journal articles that comprimised my
&lt;a class="reference external" href="http://tanbakuchi.com/Papers/2009_TanbakuchiDissertation.pdf"&gt;dissertation&lt;/a&gt;. My contribution
was the design and development of the next generation confocal microlaparascope,
software development, lens design, and clinical testing of the device with
Kenneth Hatch, Andy Rouse, and Art Gimitro. Both Art (my advisor) and
Andy were exceptional mentors and collaborators for this work. I couldn't have
done it without them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Citation: Anthony A Tanbakuchi, Joshua A Udovich, Andrew R Rouse, Kenneth D
Hatch, and Arthur F Gmitro. In vivo imaging of ovarian tissue using a
novel confocal microlaparoscope. Am J Obstet Gynecol, Oct 2010.
&lt;a class="reference external" href="http://tanbakuchi.com/Papers/2010AJOG_Clinical_Tanbakuchi.pdf"&gt;PDF&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><category>publication</category><guid>http://tanbakuchi.com/posts/in-vivo-imaging-of-ovarian-tissue-using-a-novel-confocal-microlaparoscope/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2010 12:17:07 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>